(Sheldon:)How often have we had to leave
a movie theater...
(Sheldon:)...because I got a headache
from drinking the Icee too fast?
(Sheldon:)- I can't go.
- Then don't go.
(Sheldon:)How can you say that? The scientific
opportunity of a lifetime presents itself...
...my best friend says, "Don't go."
- All right, then go.
- Listen to you.
(Sheldon:)How can I possibly go?
What are the words I can say now...
(Leonard:)...to end this conversation
and let me go back to sleep?
(Sheldon:)Odd. President Seibert posed
the exact same question.
(Leonard:)How was it resolved?
(Sheldon:)It wasn't. His wife set their dogs on me
and rendered the question moot.
(Howard:)Just imagine. If he says yes...
(Howard:)...we'll have an entire summer
without Sheldon.
(Raj:)We could play outside.
(Howard:)We could sit
on the left side of the couch.
I could use the bathroom at 8:20.